Guide to the Steinway & Sons Oral History
Steinway & Sons Oral History
- Tetzlaff, Gustav C.
  - Tetzlaff, Gustav C., 1978 June 7; OHIV 709 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 117 mins; Transcript Page Count: 43 pages
    St. Petersburg, FL
    Tetzlaff, Gustav C.
- Tureck, Rosalyn
  - Tureck, Rosalyn, 1978 August 31; OHIV 724 a-c; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 97 mins; Transcript Page Count: 51 pages
    Tureck, Rosalyn, 1914-2003
- Turowski, Henry
  - Turowski, Henry, 1978 July 28; OHIV 714 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 38 mins; Transcript Page Count: 27 pages
    Turowski, Henryk, 1898-1989
- Tyner, McCoy
  - Tyner, McCoy, 1978 October 22; OHIV 741 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 15 mins; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
    Tyner, McCoy, 1938-
- Ultes, Carl Thomas Jr. (Tom)
  - Ultes, Carl Thomas Jr. (Tom), 1979 May 7; OHIV 792 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 18 mins; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
    Springfield, OH
    Ultes, Carl Thomas (Tom), Jr.
- Vietor, Marjorie C. (Mrs. Friederick A.)
  - Vietor, Marjorie C. (Mrs. Friederick A.), 1979 January 15; OHIV 768 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 100 mins; Transcript Page Count: 71 pages
    Woodbury, CT
    Vietor, Marjorie C.
- Vronsky, Vitya
  - Vronsky, Vitya, 1980 April 1; OHIV 817 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
    Vronsky, Vitya
- Walsh, Frank
  - Walsh, Frank, 1978 June 8; OHIV 708 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 111 mins; Transcript Page Count: 62 pages
    Englewood, FL
    Walsh, Frank P.
- Werlein, Philip
  - Werlein, Philip, 1979 February 9; OHIV 776 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
    New Orleans, LA
    Werlein, Philip
- Williams, Doug
  - Williams, Doug, 1978 November 22; OHIV 751 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 21 mins; Transcript Page Count: 12 pages
    Williams, Doug
- Zeigler, Julia
  - Zeigler, Julia, 1974 June 1; OHIV 822 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 61 mins; Transcript Page Count: 50 pages
    Corona, NY
    Zeigler, Julia
- Ziegler, John Cantwell
  - Ziegler, John Cantwell, 1979 April 10; OHIV 785 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 54 mins; Transcript Page Count: 33 pages
    Ziegler, John Cantwell
- Ziegler, Henry Steinway
  - Ziegler, Henry Steinway, 1979 April 12; OHIV 787 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 64 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages